<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>UI / UX Design &#8211; SyntyTech</title>
	<atom:link href="https://cloudinteam.github.io/synty-tech/tag/ui-ux-design/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://cloudinteam.github.io/synty-tech</link>
	<description></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Mon, 30 Jan 2023 11:57:54 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.1.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://cloudinteam.github.io/synty-tech/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/favicon.png</url>
	<title>UI / UX Design &#8211; SyntyTech</title>
	<link>https://cloudinteam.github.io/synty-tech</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>SWIFT will explore asset market in 2022</title>
		<link>https://cloudinteam.github.io/synty-tech/2022/02/12/swift-will-explore-asset-market-in-2022/</link>
					<comments>https://cloudinteam.github.io/synty-tech/2022/02/12/swift-will-explore-asset-market-in-2022/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[snty-admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 12 Feb 2022 13:55:44 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[UI / UX Design]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://mthemeus.com/demos/wp/xmoze/?p=2711</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[The Crypto Volatility Index (CVI) is a decentralized solution used as a benchmark to track...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<h4>The Crypto Volatility Index (CVI) is a decentralized solution used as a benchmark to track the volatility from cryptocurrency option prices and the overall crypto market.</h4>



<p>For those who are not familiar with the term, the VIX is an index that measures volatility in the stock market based on the implied volatility of S&amp;P 500 Index options; it’s also referred to as the “Market Fear Index.”</p>



<p>In a similar way, the CVI helps users track and trade the 30-day implied volatility of Ether (ETH) Bitcoin (BTC) by using the Black-Scholes options pricing model foster an index that fluctuates between 0 and 200. Black-Scholes is a pricing model used to determine the fair price or theoretical value for a call or a put option based on six variables volatility type of optiont &amp; underlying stock pricing and risk-free rate.</p>



<h4>What Does the Platform Hold for the Future?</h4>



<p>Along with the recent migration from USDT to USDC and a recent integration with investing.com, the founders of CVI have announced the implementation of new and exciting features for the protocoler.</p>



<p>The first, is the launch of volatility tokens via CVOL (Crypto vola &amp; ETHVOL (Ethereum Volatility token). These tokens can be understood as being a wrapper for opening a long position on CVI and a tradable on Ethereum compatible DEXs. The tokens maintain their peg to the value of the underlying following a rebase mechanism with a similar architecture to that of tokens like Ampleforth. The volatility tokens can be used to benefit from arbitrage trading strategies on other compatible DEXs.</p>



<blockquote class="wp-block-quote"><p>“Learning how cryptocurrency works is like learning a new language. It is incredibly difficult at the beginning, but once it clicks it will stick with you forever.”</p></blockquote>



<figure class="is-layout-flex wp-block-gallery-1 wp-block-gallery has-nested-images columns-default is-cropped">
<figure class="wp-block-image size-full"><img decoding="async" width="398" height="280" data-id="3526"  src="https://cloudinteam.github.io/synty-tech/wp-content/uploads/2022/02/blog-detail-02-1.png" alt="" class="wp-image-3526"/></figure>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img decoding="async" width="398" height="280" data-id="3525"  src="https://cloudinteam.github.io/synty-tech/wp-content/uploads/2022/02/blog-detail-01.png" alt="" class="wp-image-3525"/></figure>
</figure>



<h4>Key Takeaways</h4>



<ul><li>The Index allows DeFi users to either hedge against or profit from volatility in the crypto market.</li><li>The index functions as a crypto version of the VIX (The S&amp;P 500 Volatility Index), a real-time for market index representing the market&#8217;s expectations for volatility forover the coming 30 days.</li><li>The index functions as a crypto version of the VIX (The S&amp;P 500 Volatility Index), a real-time for market index representing the market&#8217;s expectations for volatility forover the coming 30 days.</li></ul>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://cloudinteam.github.io/synty-tech/2022/02/12/swift-will-explore-asset-market-in-2022/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
